videos that will make you
wealthy and debt free
hi there justin also known as mr ching
positive thank you very much for
subscribing this channel thank you very
much for making it reach 900 000.
if you haven't subscribed please do
click subscribe don't forget to click
the bell button subscribe
and this video at the same time will not
be possible if it wasn't for our friends
this video is brought to you by sunlight
philippines
125 years of being the filipino's
lifetime partner to a brighter future
visit sunlife.com.ph
to know more about their insurance and
investment products and follow at
sunlight ph on facebook twitter and
instagram
[Music]
we are suffering what we call as a
health crisis
how much will it cost you when you get
sick of stroke stroke at least 1.8
million pesos
diagnosis treatment rehabilitation
at least
[Music]
beneficiaries
in case of premature ending of a life of
a person no
purpose
or let's say pending medical expenses
to make sure to make sure just in case
i always tell people prevention is
better than cure okay it happened to me
uh in
2008 when when my wife gave birth to our
third and youngest child not gonna come
in and complications
after giving birth to cut the long story
short 21 days camiso hospital
now i see you chef one in seven days
comatose fun and seven days so um
[Music]
as a medical expenses
right now we're going to talk about the
advantages of life insurance number one
um
instant access to a large amount of
money just in case of a tragedy
viva and entered talaga benefiting life
insurance is flexible for you
some people will say it's part of the
annuity
no no no yes i know it's like the gustos
is part of our protection and second
life insurance
[Music]
or life
you should be the judge
with regards to your personal finance
and your retirement pakis
well the good news is i have an online
course that will really open your mind
and teach you on how you can retire at
50. how to retire at 50.
life and health insurance is one of the
most important topics that is covered on
your retirement
ladies and gentlemen
you will retire broke and poor but if
you want to avoid that i suggest that
you check out my online course called
how to retire at 50 because in this
online course we will teach you on how
to invest and grow your money how to
invest your money in the stock market
mutual fund uitf property
form of investment at secessionato we
will also share with you on how you can
also protect yourself from scams
retirement money so if you are
interested to know more on how to retire
at 50 join me on my online course
mcconnell point investment your
investment in this course is only 799
pesos yes you heard it right 799. this
online course will open your mind so
that you will be able to retire early
and retire rich so if you want to be
part of this online course called how to
retire 50 type the word called retire
type the word called retire right now
inside your comment box after this
broadcast i will send you a link so that
you'll be able to enroll and register
thank you very much for watching if you
like this video please click like on
this video and share this video with
other people
priority health insurance or life
insurance thank you very much this
chinkitan saying to every problem
there's always a solution if you're not
part of the solution you're part of the
problem always think positive get a
chance to win one of 125 celebration
packages and create lifetime memories
with your by subway email phil dash
marketing at sunlife.com with the
subject 125th celebration promo to know
more about the promo
[Music]
thank you for watching if you want to
keep on growing and to stay inspired
subscribe and hit the bell button to get
notified always change positive
[Music]